sometimes the will develop
the to blackmail
the to And this
isn't unique to If
anything this is worse
than other models These
are things that we
don't train the in
the right way can
emerge But we've the
science of looking inside
them so we can
diagnose them and prevent
the models from happening
and retrain the so
they don't behave in
this way That said
this is something we
have to be about
We've supported various
light touch
focused measures for making
sure that all the
have to talk about
the tests that they
run We always disclose
our tests We always
basically we try and
our models to try
and really strain them
and get them to
do the worst things
possible in a test
environment so that they
never do those things
in the real world